(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) School food is bad.
It tastes fake.
It is unhealthy.
Melanie brings lunch from home instead.
She brings something different every day.
Sometimes she makes a sandwich.
Sandwiches are easy to make.
They are tasty too.
Sometimes her mom makes her home-cooked meals.
Her mom is a good chef.
Sometimes she goes to restaurants in the morning.
Then she brings the food to school.
Melanie's friends are jealous of her.
They look at her food whenever it is
lunchtime.
It smells so good.
Melanie always gives a little bit of her
food to them.
She suggests that they bring lunch from home.
They say no.
School food is free for them.